longandfoster.com 2007-12-16

# Privacy Policy

  |    | 

UNI-9

[ Home](http://www.longandfoster.com/index.aspx) > [About Us](http://www.longandfoster.com/About_Us/about_us.aspx) > Privacy Policy

Use our various search options to find your next home, vacation getaway, or commercial property. 

[Power-Search®](http://homes.longandfoster.com/Real-Estate/Power-Search.aspx?mode=cityCounty "Real Estate Search")|[Map Search](http://homes.longandfoster.com/Real-Estate/Map-Search.aspx "Beta Map Search")New!|[ Quick Search](http://homes.longandfoster.com/Real-Estate/Quick-Search-for-Homes.aspx "Houses for Sale") [Lake Search](http://homes.longandfoster.com/Real-Estate/Vacation-Power-Search.aspx?Vacation=DeepCreek "Vacation Home Search")| [Open House Search](http://homes.longandfoster.com/Real-Estate/Open-House.aspx?sec=Buying "Real Estate for Sale")| [ Classic Search](http://homes.longandfoster.com/Real-Estate/Classic-Search.aspx "Houses for Sale") [ Property Search²](http://homes.longandfoster.com/BetaSearches/Power-Search.aspx?mode=cityCounty "Beta Property Search")Beta|[ Quick Search²](http://homes.longandfoster.com/BetaSearches/Quick-Search-for-Homes.aspx "Beta Quick Search")Beta

[Extraordinary Properties](http://homes.longandfoster.com/Real-Estate/Extraordinary_Properties.aspx "Extraordinary Properties Search")®

Learn everything you need to know about selling your property, from listing your home to closing the deal. 

[ Extraordinary Properties](http://homes.longandfoster.com/Real-Estate/EP-Selling.aspx "Extraordinary Properties")® 

Whether you’re renting a primary residence or looking for a vacation getaway, we offer great selection and outstanding value. 

[Power-Search](http://homes.longandfoster.com/Real-Estate/Power-Search.aspx?SearchCategory=Rental&sec=Renting "Rental Home Search")®

Long & Foster has financing for your home purchase covered with our mortgage company Prosperity Mortgage. 

Buying a home is just the beginning of the homeownership experience. Find out how to maintain, upgrade, and protect your home. 

Long & Foster has a presence in seven states and the District of Columbia. Check out what the diverse Mid-Atlantic region has to offer. 

Jump start your career with Long & Foster, the largest privately-owned real estate company in America. 

##  Privacy Policy

Your Privacy is Very Important to Us

Long & Foster places the highest importance upon maintaining your privacy when you use our Web site. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. This privacy policy applies to the use of longandfoster.com by consumers. We review this privacy policy on an annual basis and we welcome any suggestions you might have about additional ideas regarding our privacy policy at  [ privacy@longandfoster.com](mailto:privacy@longandfoster.com).

About our Site 

This is the Web site of the Long & Foster® Companies. Our postal address is: 11351 Random Hills Road, Fairfax, Virginia, 22030. 

We can be reached via e-mail at [privacy@longandfoster.com](mailto:privacy@longandfoster.com). 

What information is collected from me? 

For each visitor to our Web site, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible). 

The information we collect consists of the following: 

  * The domain name (but not the e-mail address of visitors to our Web page). 
  * Aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit. 
  * User-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit. 
  * The e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail. 
  * Information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations. 

The information we collect is used only to improve the content of our Web site and to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor. 

Cookies

We use cookies to: 

  * Store visitors’ preferences. 
  * Record session information, such as items that consumers add to their user profile. 
  * Customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends. 

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us an email at [privacy@longandfoster.com](mailto:privacy@longandfoster.com).   

Ad Servers

We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. 

Changes & Corrections

From time to time, we make our customer e-mail list available to Long & Foster's Prestige Partners® (such as Prosperity Mortgage and Long & Foster Insurance) whose products or services we think you might find interesting. If you do not want us to share your e-mail address with other Long & Foster Real Estate, Inc, simply choose to "opt out" of these mailing by unchecking the appropriate box when providing your email address to us. If you already submitted our email address and did not opt-out of further mailing you may do so by letting us know by sending us an e-mail at [privacy@longandfoster.com](mailto:privacy@longandfoster.com). 

If you supply us with your postal address online you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by sending us an e-mail at the address listed above. Please provide us with your exact name and address. We will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with our partners. 

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers online will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding inquiries they have placed online. 

Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in any personal information they have volunteered or in any communications that the consumer/visitor has directed to the site. Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us an e-mail at the address listed above. 

Policy Changes

Occasionally we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically. 

Data Security

We always use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. 

Scope of This Privacy Policy

This privacy policy only applies to longandfoster.com. The site contains links to sites operated and maintained by third parties over which we have absolutely no control. Please be aware that these sites may collect information about you, and operate according to their own privacy practices that may differ from this privacy policy. Remember that once you are outside the sites, any information you submit is outside of our control. 

Questions or Concerns

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, you may contact us by sending us an e-mail at [privacy@longandfoster.com](mailto:privacy@longandfoster.com). 

|    |     
---|---|---|---|---
